

# Rei Koleci

## Front end Developer - React

Tirana, Albania 355 69 72 99 742 · <u>rkoleci14@gmail.com</u>

Portfolio, Github,Linkedin, Upwork

Skills

React

NextJs

RemixRun

React Native

Redux

React-Query

GraphQL

RestAPI

TS

Pure CSS

Git

JIRA

Languages

English

**Hobbies** 

Supercars Test Drive

### **Profile**

Experienced React developer with 4 years of professional work and a portfolio of different projects within React and its frameworks.

I hold a Master degree in Computer Science and I am based in Tirana, Albania

Consider myself a team member responsible to ship quality code within deadlines.

# **Employment History**

Frontend Developer React.js (Remote), Cyabra, Israel

May 2022

Member of Front end team that is responsible for admin panel of the social media AI analyser

Writing unit tests, code review and UI enhancements

Regular bug fixing

Moved API calls from redux(action, reducers) to react-query

Added dark mode support based on styled-components theme

SSR React.js Dev RemixRun (Remote), GetHalal.de, Hamburg, Germany

March 2022 — June 2022

Member of Front end team responsible for ecommerce storefront

Building features: Cart, Checkout, Email Reset, GridLists

Query and mutations using GraphQL

UI using ChakraUI, based on Figma

Contributed in the Payout feature flow

Code review, ensure coding structure for other devs

Added support for responsivity on legacy views

React Native Dev (Remote), Persona, US

April 2020 — October 2022

Setup boilerplate using Expo

Build UI based on Figma

Integration with Rest API

Build custom Native nav based on v6

Handled auth flow with token

Build a Schedule feature

#### Frontend/SSR Dev CRA/Next.js, Sisal.it, Tirana

November 2019 — February 2022

Improve legacy websites, part of a major online betting company

Update certain features, mostly UI

Regular bug fixing

Fixed bugs on redux, mui, react class components

Created new UI using mui, css

Implemented reusable components using SOLID principles

#### React Admin Dev (On-site), AT Consulting, Tirana

October 2018 - November 2019

Member of Front end team on React

Contribute on an admin dashboard site

Create interface for a CRM (CoreBOS)

Fetch data from CRM and display on site

Created an abstraction of MUI Datatable, custom to the CRM

Redux to manage global state

### **Education**

Computer Engineering Bsc, Epoka University, Tirana

October 2014 - June 2017

Master of Arts Computer Science, Epoka University, Tirana

November 2017 - May 2018